export default [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'How many seasons of Friends are there?',
    answer: 'Ten seasons.'
  },

  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'Joey played Dr. Drake Ramoray on which soap opera show?',
    answer: 'Days of Our Lives.'
  },

  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'How many times did Ross get divorced?',
    answer: 'Three.'
  },

  { id: 4, question: 'What store does Phoebe hate?', answer: 'Pottery Barn.' },

  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'Rachel got a job with which company in Paris?',
    answer: 'Louis Vuitton.'
  },

  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'What are the names of Ross and Monica’s parents?',
    answer: 'Jack and Judy Geller.'
  },

  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'What was the occupation of Rachel’s fiancé Barry Farber?',
    answer: 'Orthodontist.'
  },

  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'Who was the maid of honor at Monica’s wedding?',
    answer: 'Rachel.'
  },

  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'Phoebe’s scientist boyfriend David worked in what city?',
    answer: 'Minsk.'
  },

  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'Monica dated an ophthalmologist named?',
    answer: 'Richard.'
  },

  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'Which Sprouse brother played Ross’ son Ben?',
    answer: 'Cole.'
  },

  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'True or false, Rachel kissed all of her Friends (male and female) on the show?',
    answer: 'True.'
  },

  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'What is Chandler Bing’s middle name?',
    answer: 'Muriel.'
  },

  {
    id: 14,
    question: 'Who pees on Monica after she is stung by a jellyfish?',
    answer: 'Chandler.'
  },

  {
    id: 15,
    question: 'What is the name of Phoebe’s twin sister?',
    answer: 'Ursula.'
  },

  {
    id: 16,
    question: 'Ross says whose name at the altar in London?',
    answer: 'Rachel.'
  },

  {
    id: 17,
    question: 'Which member of the British royal family appeared on Friends?',
    answer: 'Sarah Ferguson/Duchess of York.'
  },

  {
    id: 18,
    question: 'Brad Pitt and David Schwimmer’s characters cofounded what club in high school?',
    answer: 'The “I Hate Rachel Green Club.”'
  },

  {
    id: 19,
    question: 'Which of Joey’s sisters did Chandler fool around with?',
    answer: 'Mary Angela.'
  },

  {
    id: 20,
    question: 'Who was Joey’s imaginary childhood friend? ',
    answer: 'Maurice.'
  },

  {
    id: 21,
    question: 'What was the profession of Joey’s imaginary friend?',
    answer: 'Space cowboy.'
  },

  {
    id: 22,
    question: 'What was Monica’s nickname when she was a field hockey goalie?',
    answer: 'Big Fat Goalie.'
  },

  {
    id: 23,
    question: 'What does Rachel guess Chandler’s job is?',
    answer: 'A transponster.'
  },

  {
    id: 24,
    question: 'What is Richard’s daughter’s name?',
    answer: 'Michelle.'
  },

  { id: 25, question: 'Who is Joey’s agent?', answer: 'Estelle.' },

  {
    id: 26,
    question: 'Who mistakingly threw a woman’s wooden leg into a fire?',
    answer: 'Joey.'
  },

  {
    id: 27,
    question: 'What was the name of Chandler and Ross’ college band?',
    answer: 'Way, No Way.'
  },

  {
    id: 28,
    question: 'Monica categorizes her towels into how many categories?',
    answer: '11.'
  },

  {
    id: 29,
    question: 'Ross and Rachel’s wedding dinner was held where in Vegas?',
    answer: 'A Pizza Hut.'
  },

  {
    id: 30,
    question: 'Joey and Chandler’s TV guide is addressed to who?',
    answer: 'Miss Chanandler Bong.'
  },

  {
    id: 31,
    question: 'What was the name of Ross’ pet monkey?',
    answer: 'Marcel.'
  },

  {
    id: 32,
    question: 'According to Monica, a woman has how many erogenous zones?',
    answer: 'Seven.'
  },

  {
    id: 33,
    question: 'What does Phoebe legally change her name to after her wedding?',
    answer: 'Princess Consulea Banana Hammock.'
  },

  {
    id: 34,
    question: 'What form of self-defense does Ross try to teach Rachel and Phoebe?',
    answer: 'Unagi.'
  },

  {
    id: 35,
    question: 'What song makes Ross and Rachel’s daughter Emma laugh for the first time?',
    answer: 'Sir Mix-a-Lot’s “Baby Got Back.”'
  },

  {
    id: 36,
    question: 'What is the name of Joey’s stuffed penguin?',
    answer: 'Hugsy.'
  },

  {
    id: 37,
    question: 'What caused the fire at Rachel and Phoebe’s apartment?',
    answer: 'Rachel’s hair straightener.'
  },

  {
    id: 38,
    question: 'Phoebe is a surrogate for who?',
    answer: 'Her half-brother Frank Jr. and his wife Alice.'
  },

  { id: 39, question: 'What color is Monica’s apartment?', answer: 'Purple.' },

  { id: 40, question: 'How many sisters does Joey have?', answer: 'Seven.' },

  { id: 41, question: 'Joey doesn’t share what?', answer: 'Food.' },

  {
    id: 42,
    question: 'What do Monica and Chandler name their twins?',
    answer: 'Erica and Jack.'
  },

  {
    id: 43,
    question: 'Ross’ first wife Carol leaves him for who?',
    answer: 'Susan Bunch.'
  },

  {
    id: 44,
    question: 'What is the name of Chandler’s father’s Las Vegas all-male burlesque?',
    answer: 'Viva Las Gaygas.'
  },

  {
    id: 45,
    question: 'Phoebe attempts to teach Joey what language?',
    answer: 'French.'
  },

  {
    id: 46,
    question: 'Chick Jr. and Duck Jr. got stuck in what?',
    answer: 'A foosball table.'
  },

  {
    id: 47,
    question: 'Who was married to a supposedly gay Canadian ice dancer named Duncan?',
    answer: 'Phoebe.'
  },

  {
    id: 48,
    question: 'Rachel was in which sorority?',
    answer: 'Kappa Kappa Delta.'
  },

  {
    id: 49,
    question: 'What are the names of Rachel’s sisters?',
    answer: 'Jill and Amy Greene.'
  },

  {
    id: 50,
    question: 'Which character famously said, “PIVOT?”',
    answer: 'Ross.'
  },

  {
    id: 51,
    question: 'Phoebe finds what in her soda can?',
    answer: 'A human thumb.'
  },

  {
    id: 52,
    question: 'Who was (accidentally) Monica’s first kiss?',
    answer: 'Her brother Ross.'
  },

  {
    id: 53,
    question: 'Rachel goes on Ross’ honeymoon by herself where?',
    answer: 'Athens, Greece.'
  },

  {
    id: 54,
    question: 'What holiday does Chandler hate?',
    answer: 'Thanksgiving.'
  },

  { id: 55, question: 'Who was Rachel’s prom date?', answer: 'Chip Matthews.' },

  {
    id: 56,
    question: 'What was the name of Ross and Monica’s dog when they were kids?',
    answer: 'Chi-Chi.'
  },

  {
    id: 57,
    question: 'What actor played Phoebe’s husband Mike Hannigan?',
    answer: 'Paul Rudd.'
  },

  {
    id: 58,
    question: 'Where did Ross and Rachel have their first date?',
    answer: 'The planetarium.'
  },

  { id: 59, question: 'How many roses did Ross send Emily?', answer: '72.' },

  {
    id: 60,
    question: 'How many pages was Rachel’s letter to Ross?',
    answer: 'Eighteen pages (front and back).'
  },

  {
    id: 61,
    question: 'What year did Friends first premiere?',
    answer: '1994.'
  },

  {
    id: 61,
    question: 'Joey’s Cabbage Patch Kid is named what?',
    answer: 'Alicia May Emory'
  },

  {
    id: 62,
    question: 'What was the name of the game Chandler made up to give Joey money?',
    answer: 'Cups.'
  },

  {
    id: 63,
    question: 'In an effort to get over Richard, Monica started making what?',
    answer: 'Jam.'
  },

  { id: 64, question: 'What fruit is Ross allergic to?', answer: 'Kiwi.' },

  { id: 65, question: 'What is Rachel’s favorite flower?', answer: 'Lillies.' },

  {
    id: 66,
    question: 'What was the name of Ross and Rachel’s male nanny?',
    answer: 'Sandy.'
  },

  {
    id: 67,
    question: 'Who came on to who in The One With The Videotape?',
    answer: 'Rachel came on to Ross.'
  },

  {
    id: 68,
    question: 'What was Joey’s nickname when he was working at Alessandro’s?',
    answer: 'Dragon.'
  },

  {
    id: 69,
    question: 'Monica worked as a waitress at what diner?',
    answer: 'Moondance Diner.'
  },

  { id: 70, question: 'What was Rachel’s bra size?', answer: '32C.' },

  {
    id: 71,
    question: 'Ross worked as a professor at what school?',
    answer: 'New York University.'
  },

  {
    id: 72,
    question: 'What word did Rachel misspell on her resume?',
    answer: 'Computer.'
  },

  {
    id: 73,
    question: 'What are the names of the triplets Phoebe gives birth to?',
    answer: 'Frank Jr. Jr., Leslie and Chandler.'
  },

  { id: 74, question: 'Who said, “See, he’s her lobster!”', answer: 'Phoebe.' },

  {
    id: 75,
    question: 'What city is Friends set in?',
    answer: 'New York City.'
  },

  {
    id: 76,
    question: 'What is the first wedding gift Monica opens?',
    answer: 'A tiny salt shaker.'
  },

  {
    id: 77,
    question: 'Rachel’s sister Amy decides she wants to become what after babysitting Emma?',
    answer: 'A baby stylist.'
  },

  {
    id: 78,
    question: 'Ross and Carol were busted having sex on which Disney ride?',
    answer: 'It’s a Small World.'
  },

  {
    id: 79,
    question: 'Which Friend entered a Vanilla Ice lookalike contest and won?',
    answer: 'Chandler.'
  },

  {
    id: 80,
    question: 'True or false, Monica ate macaroni off a jewelry box she made.',
    answer: 'True.'
  },

  {
    id: 81,
    question: 'What ingredient did Rachel mistakingly put in her Thanksgiving trifle?',
    answer: 'Beef.'
  },

  {
    id: 82,
    question: 'Phoebe thought “Kenny the Copy Guy” was who?',
    answer: 'Ralph Lauren.'
  },

  {
    id: 83,
    question: 'What is the name of Joey’s barcalounger?',
    answer: 'Rosita.'
  },

  {
    id: 84,
    question: 'Who dated a college student named Elizabeth Stevens?',
    answer: 'Ross.'
  },

  {
    id: 85,
    question: 'Monica could not tell time until what age?',
    answer: '13.'
  },

  {
    id: 86,
    question: 'Phoebe created a three-dimensional picture of a woman named?',
    answer: 'Gladys.'
  },

  {
    id: 87,
    question: 'Who was the last Friend to find out about Monica and Chandler’s relationship?',
    answer: 'Ross.'
  },

  {
    id: 88,
    question: 'Chandler and Joey both dated an actress named?',
    answer: 'Kathy.'
  },

  {
    id: 89,
    question: 'What did Monica want from Phoebe as an engagement present?',
    answer: 'Her grandmother‘s cookie recipe.'
  },

  {
    id: 90,
    question: 'Who had a pony and a boat at age 15?',
    answer: 'Rachel.'
  },

  {
    id: 91,
    question:
      'Phoebe said something was wrong with the right or the left phalange of Rachel’s plane?',
    answer: 'The left.'
  },

  {
    id: 92,
    question: 'Who is Santa’s friend that Ross invents to teach Ben about Hanukkah?',
    answer: 'The Holiday Armadillo.'
  },

  { id: 93, question: 'Who is the youngest Friend?', answer: 'Rachel.' },

  {
    id: 94,
    question: 'Chandler told Janice he was moving where to avoid seeing her again?',
    answer: 'Yemen.'
  },

  { id: 95, question: 'Who introduced Phoebe and Mike?', answer: 'Joey.' },

  {
    id: 96,
    question: 'Phoebe’s grandmother said she got her cookie recipe from her grandmother named?',
    answer: 'Nestle Toulouse (AKA Nestlé Toll House).'
  },

  {
    id: 97,
    question: 'The Geller Cup was a trophy for which sport?',
    answer: 'Touch football games.'
  },

  {
    id: 98,
    question: 'Joey’s stalker Erika Ford was played by which actress?',
    answer: 'Brooke Shields.'
  },

  {
    id: 99,
    question: 'Who did Monica forget to invite to Rachel’s baby shower?',
    answer: 'Rachel’s mother Sandra.'
  },

  {
    id: 100,
    question: 'Which of Monica’s boyfriends wanted to become the Ultimate Fighting Champion?',
    answer: 'Pete (Peter Becker).'
  },

  {
    id: 101,
    question:
      'What was the name of the lipstick brand for men that Joey starred in a Japanese commercial for?',
    answer: 'Ichiban.'
  },

  {
    id: 102,
    question: 'Ross, Susan and Phoebe got stuck where before Ben’s birth?',
    answer: 'A closet.'
  },

  {
    id: 103,
    question: 'Who gave Phoebe away at her wedding?',
    answer: 'Chandler.'
  },

  {
    id: 104,
    question: 'Monica and Chandler first got together where?',
    answer: 'London.'
  },

  {
    id: 105,
    question: 'The handcuffs that were found in Rachel’s former room belonged to who?',
    answer: 'Monica and Ross’ Nana (grandmother).'
  },

  {
    id: 106,
    question: 'Chandler and Ross helped Joey practice for what game show audition?',
    answer: 'Bamboozled.'
  },

  {
    id: 107,
    question: 'What does Chandler call the Paris of Oklahoma?',
    answer: 'Tulsa.'
  },

  {
    id: 108,
    question: 'What food caused Ross to get sick on Space Mountain?',
    answer: 'Tacos.'
  },

  { id: 109, question: 'Who is older Ross or Monica?', answer: 'Ross.' },

  {
    id: 110,
    question: 'What is actually Rachel’s favorite movie?',
    answer: 'Weekend at Bernie’s.'
  },

  {
    id: 111,
    question: 'Which Friend had a traumatic swing incident at age 4?',
    answer: 'Rachel.'
  },

  {
    id: 112,
    question: 'Ross and Rachel’s daughter Emma would have turned 18 what year?',
    answer: '2020.'
  },

  {
    id: 113,
    question: 'Which Friend didn’t go to London for Ross’ wedding?',
    answer: 'Phoebe.'
  },

  {
    id: 114,
    question: 'What kind of bed did the Mattress King deliver to Monica?',
    answer: 'A racecar bed.'
  },

  {
    id: 115,
    question: 'Emma’s first birthday cake was supposed to be shaped like what?',
    answer: 'A bunny.'
  },

  {
    id: 116,
    question: 'In what part of her body did Monica get a pencil stuck at age 14?',
    answer: 'Her ear.'
  },

  {
    id: 117,
    question: 'Ross created a comic book called what?',
    answer: 'Science Boy.'
  },

  { id: 118, question: 'What is Chandler’s surname?', answer: 'Bing.' },

  { id: 119, question: 'What is Joey’s favorite food?', answer: 'Sandwiches.' },

  {
    id: 120,
    question: 'How old was Chandler when he first touched a girl’s breast?',
    answer: '19.'
  },

  {
    id: 121,
    question: 'What is Monica’s biggest pet peeve?',
    answer: 'Animals dressed as humans.'
  },

  {
    id: 122,
    question: 'Which Friend had his/her identity stolen?',
    answer: 'Monica.'
  },

  {
    id: 123,
    question:
      'Joey doesn’t read which book without making sure there is plenty of room in the freezer?',
    answer: 'The Shining.'
  },

  {
    id: 124,
    question: 'What is the name of Ross and Monica’s maternal grandmother?',
    answer: 'Althea.'
  },

  {
    id: 125,
    question: 'Who stole all the insoles out of Chandler’s shoes?',
    answer: 'Chandler’s roomate Eddie.'
  },

  {
    id: 126,
    question: 'Who gave Rachel and Ross the name “Emma” for their daughter?',
    answer: 'Monica.'
  },

  {
    id: 127,
    question: 'Joey was cast as the butt double for which actor?',
    answer: 'Al Pacino.'
  },

  {
    id: 128,
    question: ' What is the name of Phoebe’s alter ego?',
    answer: 'Regina Phalange.'
  },

  {
    id: 129,
    question: 'What year did the series finale of Friends air?',
    answer: '2004.'
  },

  {
    id: 130,
    question: 'What is the name of Rachel and Monica’s building superintendent?',
    answer: 'Mr. Treeger.'
  },

  { id: 131, question: 'What is Joey’s pin number?', answer: '5639.' },

  {
    id: 132,
    question: 'What was the last state that Ross couldn’t remember?',
    answer: 'Delaware.'
  },

  {
    id: 133,
    question: 'What was the name of Chandler’s roommate prior to Joey?',
    answer: 'Kip.'
  },

  {
    id: 134,
    question: 'Whose idea was it to get married in Vegas, Rachel or Ross’?',
    answer: 'Rachel.'
  },

  {
    id: 135,
    question: 'What was the name of Monica’s imaginary boyfriend?',
    answer: 'Jared.'
  },

  {
    id: 136,
    question: 'What kind of plastic surgery did Rachel have?',
    answer: 'A nose job.'
  },

  {
    id: 137,
    question: 'Who was called Sir Limps-a-Lot after losing a toe?',
    answer: 'Chandler.'
  },

  {
    id: 138,
    question: 'What was the name of Rachel’s hairless cat?',
    answer: 'Mrs. Whiskerson.'
  },

  {
    id: 139,
    question: 'Which balloon got away during the Macy’s Thanksgiving Day Parade in Season 1?',
    answer: 'Underdog.'
  },

  {
    id: 140,
    question: 'Who gave birth to Chandler and Monica’s twins?',
    answer: 'Erica.'
  },

  {
    id: 141,
    question: 'Chandler and Rachel ate cheesecake off the floor from what bakery?  ',
    answer: 'Mama’s Little Bakery.'
  },

  { id: 142, question: 'Which Friend once mugged Ross?', answer: 'Phoebe.' },

  {
    id: 143,
    question: 'Monica, Ross and Rachel attended what high school?',
    answer: 'Lincoln High School.'
  },

  { id: 144, question: 'Who were on “a break”?', answer: 'Rachel and Ross.' },

  {
    id: 145,
    question: 'What was the name of Monica’s senior prom date?',
    answer: 'Roy Gublik.'
  },

  {
    id: 146,
    question: 'Ross was jealous of who at Rachel’s job?',
    answer: 'Mark.'
  },

  {
    id: 147,
    question: 'What was the name of the “hot girl from the Xerox place?”',
    answer: 'Chloe.'
  },

  { id: 148, question: 'What did Rachel get a tattoo of?', answer: 'A heart.' },

  {
    id: 149,
    question: 'Who is the first Friend to speak on the show?',
    answer: 'Monica.'
  },

  {
    id: 150,
    question: 'Who sings the Friends theme song “I’ll Be There for You?”',
    answer: 'The Rembrandts.'
  }
]
